hey everybody welcome to this b1 english
listening practice video you can use
this video to practice your listening
and comprehension as i speak before we
start remember to download the listening
time podcast and become a member at
patreon.comlisteningtime to receive my
listening practice seminars sound
training videos and bonus podcast
episodes okay today i'm going to talk
about some of my favorite memories from
the past this is one of the funnest
topics to talk about because we all love
reminiscing about the good old days
let's just jump right in the first
memory i want to talk about is 6th grade
camp in case you've never heard of this
before in the u.s at least when i was in
school we had the tradition of going on
a week-long camping trip during 6th
grade when i went we didn't actually
camp in tents though we got divided into
groups and stayed in different cabins
with different camp counselors who were
in charge of the cabins i had such an
awesome time because we got to do a lot
of outdoor activities like hiking
archery and rock climbing
since i'm an outdoorsy person this type
of trip was right up my alley aside from
the activities we had plenty of time to
talk play and bond with the other kids
also the food was bomb of all the
memories i have of elementary school
sixth grade camp is probably number one
alright the next memory i want to talk
about is a trip i took to hawaii when i
was 13. i've actually been to hawaii a
handful of times but this trip was
special because it was only the first or
second time that i had ever traveled
without my parents i went with a friend
and his family and we stayed in a nice
hotel right across from waikiki beach in
honolulu at that time i thought it was
the coolest thing to take a week off
school go to one of the most beautiful
places on earth and be without my
parents i guess i didn't do anything
that special on that trip but the
circumstances were what made it such a
great memory for me okay another memory
that'll always stay with me is the first
day i drove to school in my own car i
was barely 16 i had just gotten my
license the day before and i felt like i
was on top of the world i remember
having my music playlist specifically
chosen for that momentous occasion
getting your driver's license is a big
rite of passage for young americans and
it's a proud moment when you can finally
drive yourself around and not have to
rely on your parents to give you a ride
at that time i thought my car was really
cool but looking back now it wasn't all
that however that doesn't make the
memory any less important to me another
one of my top memories is graduating
from high school the ceremony itself
wasn't anything special and i wasn't
necessarily proud of myself or anything
but i was just relieved to finally be
done and not only that but at that age i
had big dreams and lofty expectations
for my future so i was excited to
finally start that journey my life
didn't end up going as i'd planned it
but that doesn't matter the reason why
graduating from high school was such a
powerful memory for me is because i can
really remember that excitement that i
felt alright perhaps my favorite memory
of the past is the language exchange
program i did in mexico in 2013. this
was the first solo experience i'd ever
had in another country there wasn't
anything that could have prepared me for
this type of trip i went to a foreign
country without being able to speak the
language well and i stayed with an older
couple who didn't speak any english
needless to say i struggled big time
during those first couple days but
little by little i started to get my
bearings i made friends i learned
spanish and i even met my future wife
even today my wife and i love going back
to some of those old spots where we hung
out during my exchange program as you
can see i really enjoy reminiscing about
the past okay that's all for today
remember to download the listening time
podcast and become a member at
patreon.comlisteningtime to receive my
listening practice seminars sound
training videos and bonus podcast
episodes also subscribe to the channel
click on the bell and follow us on
instagram i'll see you next time
[Music]
you